(Leonard:)- Maybe.
- Come on.
(Penny:)Yeah, okay, no.
(Bernadette:)Do you think you'll sleep with him
tonight?
Absolutely not. We're just gonna have
dinner and, you know, see how it goes.
(Amy:)If he were dying,
would you sleep with him?
(Penny:)What?
- Assuming he were dying...
(Amy:)...of something that couldn't
be sexually transmitted.
(Sheldon:)You know,
Iike a spear wound to the head.
(Penny:)Okay, he is not dying.
(Amy:)How do you know? Are you a doctor?
(Bernadette:)You can make-believe though.
(Bernadette:)Sometimes Howard and I pretend
that his arrhythmia is acting up...
(Bernadette:)...and I'm a sexy cardiologist...
(Bernadette:)...and the naughty part is
I'm not in his HMO network.
(Penny:)Screw it. I'm not gonna make
a big deal out of this. It's just dinner.
With a dead man. Rawr.
(Penny:)Amy, stop it.
(Penny:)Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
(Bernadette:)Relax. You know Leonard's always been
crazy about you. It's gonna be great.
(Penny:)We've finally gotten to a place where
we can hang out without it being weird.